I can say it with certainty.
In this entire world, no one is as hated by digital devices as I am.
If I touch a computer, I hit a bug.
If I touch a smartphone, it freezes.
Virus infections? All the time.
But I believe that someday, we'll be able to get along.
So please... just let today be the day.
Why does this always happen to me!?
Understand?
What we must aim for is perfection.
I want each and every one of you to be aware that you are the ones supporting this railway.
Safety and security are the keys to earning our passengers' trust.
As I've said many times: zero computer virus infections!
Zero information security incidents!
That should be a given!
And yet you can't even manage that!
Anyone who gets infected is just as guilty as the hacker!
Disciplinary action will be unavoidable, of course.
I heard someone in the International Division got demoted.
You'd better be especially careful, Mei...
Unfortunately, that concern is well-founded.
I'm next. That's what I thought.
(Katsuragi) Be aware of your duty as railway employees and devote yourselves to your work.
Awareness -- right, I need to be more aware.
Understand?
I won't get infected by viruses anymore!
Uuugh... my computer is acting weird.
She just said that and already...
We need to contact the System Division...
We'll get fired -- both you and me...
Um, Uyagawa, I'm sorry!
Could you please keep this between us?
Sure, no problem.
Just be more careful from now on, okay?
I've removed the virus.
Thank you so much!
Saved by the skin of my teeth...
Director Katsuragi isn't kidding around, you know.
You really need to be more aware
and stop causing trouble for other people.
Yes...
Ugh... of all days, today is just not my day...
Sorry, Agaho, can you get the phone?
Thank you for calling.
Kyoki Railway PR Department, Agaho speaking.
(Phone voice) My name is Asagiri Yoshimitsu.
You see, starting a few minutes ago, on our website...
We've been receiving suspicious traffic resembling a DoS attack from your IP address.
Huh!?
IP...?
DoS...koi?
It was a prank call!
Ah-- hey, wait!?
There sure are a lot of weirdos out there.
Well, at least that was a change of pace.
(Colleague) The Kobe TV crew is here.
Coming!
Is it just me, or is Tarumi not here again?
Don't worry, that's her hobby.
I think she's driving a train -- a special service.
Basically a hobby.
Doors closed, check!
Side lights, check!
Platform, check!
Departure equivalent -- proceed!
I knew it was Akane!
We're not using anything that heavy!
Hello, this is Hosono from the System Division.
We've been getting nonstop alerts since this morning.
Main Line -- 431M, 441M, 2103D!
At 9:35, upon request from National Railways--
Emergency broadcast!
Multiple signals passed at danger!
Whaaaat!? I didn't do anything!?